UNG SEREYVUTH

Plov lum, Phum 1, Sangkat Phnom Penh Thmey, Khan Sen Sok, Cambodia **Tel: (855) 17 487 157**

E-Mail: sereyvuth_ung@yahoo.com

May 23, 2018

Wing (Cambodia) Limited Specialized Bank

Tel: (855) 23 999 989

E-Mail: jobs@wingmoney.com

Dear Sir/Madam,

Your job announcement on PELPREK.COM for the position of **Digital Marketing Manager** truly took my attention. I would like very much in applying for this position at your company.

Presently, I am working as a **Senior Web Developer & Team Leader** at GIGB Business Investment (Cambodia) Co., ltd. Also, I've completed Master of Business Administration (**MBA**) at **Norton University.** In addition, I took two bachelor degrees, **Bachelor of Informatics Economics** at **Royal University of Law and Economics** and **Bachelor of English for Communication** at **Norton University**.

I'm interested in working in this position because I will have an opportunity to implement all my existing knowledge of **over-6-year working experiences** relatively with social media management, app development, web development and SEO, paid media strategy development, and it will also strongly help me to gain more experiences from your company. I'm sure that I am able to perform all tasks mentioned in the job announcement smoothly since I am a leading talented and high responsible person with **very good English knowledge**. I will appreciate to have a chance to demonstrate my exact ability.

I would strongly appreciate an opportunity to meet you to discuss my interest. I will be available at your convenience.

Please do not hesitate to contact me for an interview.

I look forward to hearing from you and thank you for your kind considerations.

Yours Faithfully,

UNG SEREYVUTH

CURRICULUM VITAE

UNG SEREYVUTH

Plov lum, Phum 1, Sangkat Phnom Penh Thmey, Khan Sen Sok, Cambodia **Tel:** (855) 17 487 157

Email: sereyvuth_ung@yahoo.com



PERSONAL PROFILE

Nationality : Cambodian

Sex : Male Marital Status : Single

Date of Birth : January 12, 1989

Place of Birth : Takeo Province, Cambodia

A motivated, adaptable and responsible computing graduate seeking a position in a **Digital Marketing Manager** position which will utilize the professional and technical skills developed through past 6-year working experiences.

EDUCATIONAL BACKGROUND

13/04/2013 - 30/03/2017	: Master of Business Administration (MBA) at
	Norton University, Phnom Penh, Cambodia.
09/09/2007 - 01/09/2011	: Bachelor of Informatics Economics (IE) at Royal University of
	Laws and Economics, Phnom Penh, Cambodia (Scholarship)
09/09/2007 - 04/06/2011	: Bachelor of English for Communication at Norton
	University, Phnom Penh, Cambodia.
2004-2007	: High School Degree with grade B (99.719) at Somdach Ov
	High School, Takeo Province, Cambodia.
2001-2004	: Secondary School degree at Somdach Ov High School, Takeo
	Province, Cambodia.
1995-2001	: Primary School degree at Bort roka Primary School, Takeo
	Province, Cambodia.

ACHIEVEMENTS

23/07/2008	: Passed Vietnam's Government Scholarship.
06/08/2007	: Got full scholarship from the government for Bachelor of
	Informatics Economics at RULE for academic year: 2007-2011.
04/04/2007	: Got the 1 st class of clever student examination of Annual National
	Clever Student for the Province Level on Mathematics subject.

EXPERIENCES

<u>01/01/2015 – Present</u> : **Senior IT & Development Team Leader** at **GIGB Business Investment (Cambodia) Co., ltd.,** Phnom Penh, Cambodia.

- Lead IT development team and prepared weekly report to director
- Monitor and trained new IT staff
- Coordinate the projects and present to clients
- Instructor in project training events
- Develop Advanced Web-based systems (create my own web framework)

- Company representative on seminar events
- Web master / server administrator and solved overall project problems
- Keep up to date with the latest technologies

<u>01/10/2013 – 31/12/2014</u> : **IT Development Team Leader** at **SDBS Technology Co., ltd** (**SDBS**), Phnom Penh, Cambodia.

- Led IT development team and prepared weekly report to director
- Monitored and trained new IT staff
- Developed Web-based trading system (Binary Option Platform + CRM system) and other advanced web-based systems
- Developed mobile application (hybrid version)
- Kept up to date with the latest technologies

<u>05/12/2011 – 30/09/2013</u> : **IT Official** at **Securities and Exchange Commission of Cambodia (SECC)**, Phnom Penh.

- Led IT development team and prepared report to manager
- Developed online reporting system and Windows application (VB.net)
- Kept up to date with the latest technologies

<u>01/09/2011 – 01/04/2012</u> : **Web Developer** at **GreenWebSolution Co.,Ltd**, PP. (Part Time)

- Developed general dynamic websites
- Met clients for website requirements

15/07/2011 – 05/12/2011 : **IT Officer** at **Princess Hotel**, Phnom Penh.

- Monitored general IT tasks
- Maintenance hotel website
- Maintenance exist hotel network infrastructure and technical devices

<u>01/03/2011 - 12/07/2011</u> : Interned on Web Design project at **Sambath Tip Guesthouse and Restaurant**, Phnom Penh.

- Met guesthouse manager for website requirements
- Developed and hosted guesthouse website

<u>01/07/2010 - 30/09/2010</u> : Interned as an **IT Network Assistant** at Statistic Department of **Ministry of Planning**, Phnom Penh.

- Configured and test local network in the office room
- Data entry

TRAINING PROGRAMS

<u>11/11/2017 – 18/02/2018</u> : Joint IOS Mobile App Development (Swift 4)

25/05/2014 – 30/05/2014 : Joint "**Information Security**" exhibition at Coex Hall, Seoul,

South Korea.

01/07/2010 – 12/12/2010 : Completed **Web Development Skill** at **IT City Computer**

Center, Phnom Penh.

OTHER SKILLS

1. Languages:

.Khmer: (Native Language)

.English (Bachelor Degree): Very Good

- 2. Web & Computer Programming Knowledge:
 - E-Commerce
 - Social media management & Search Engine Optimizer (SEO)

- Binary Option Platform (Real-Time Trading System + CRM system)
- Online Reporting System (Report & Document Management)
- Reservation System
- Data Entry and Data Management System (Windows Application VB.net)
- Web Development (HTML, JavaScript, jQuery, Ajax, CSS, PHP, MySQL, etc.)
- General graphic and media editing programs
- OOP

INTEREST

- 1. Making Communication with People.
- 2. Reading Book and Newspaper.
- 3. Playing Sport.
- 4. Listening to Radio and New Things in the World.
- 5. Surfing on the Internet for the new knowledge, especially technology.

REFEREES

1. Mr. Chhay Khunlong

Professor at Royal University of Law and Economics Tel: 012 32 73 73

161. 012 32 13 13

2. Mr. Sum Sry

Director at VOKC News

Tel: 012 77 30 10







tie ener ilierentite ilientissneitenäti

18 Pe	क्राहिन्ने
	ಗಾತ್ರಿಕ್ಕಾರ್
धं कक्ष	ಕ್ಷಾಕ್ರಾಭ್

សេចភ្លិចម្លួចសំបុគ្របញ្ជាក់កំណើត

ចម្លងសំបុត្របញ្ច	ា្កក់កំណើតចេញ <u></u> ពី	ស្សេវភៅបញ្ជាក់កំណើត លេខ ២៩/២០០៥		พบุธบญกล่างเกิด ในสังเรียรี ค.ค.เอลสุภ.มูาใน00.2							
នាមត្រកូល			ភេទ								
នាមខ្លួនអ្នកកើត		की	FF.	رهريخ							
പ്രംയം വേണ്ടി	នាមត្រកូល	UNG	UNG								
ជាអក្សរឡាតាំង	នាមខ្លួនអ្នកកើត	SEREYVUTH									
សញ្ជាតិ			हुन -								
ថ្ងៃ ខែ ឆ្នាំកំណើត	TUBLE	हुई कु है विव हुन लार ये की विदार्									
	ងកំណើត ខណ្ឌ ខេត្តក្រុង ប្រទេស	रम्बत मुख्य थे वर्षम मान्य योहन या क्षित्र है। वेश्वर क्षित्र के									
គុំ ពុក	ម្ដាយ	គី ពុក	भू	ម្តាយ							
នាមត្រកូល និង នាមខ្ល	9	इस वहर	में था ।	नदीत .							
ជាអ្នក្សរឡាតាំង											
សញ្ជាតិ	Mary M	går	Ĕ3	695							
ថ្ងៃ ខែឆ្នាំកំណើត		्रिकार्य ६५ मान् इन्	म्बर्टि हिंदी निर्देश	हो हो जा है कि हा है है							
	ងកំណើត ខណ្ឌ ខេត្តក្រុង ប្រទេស	विश्व के विषय के के किया में	रेन्ड्र ज्वर ज्वर १न्ड्र ज्वर ज्वर (त्वपुन ज								
nos ava son		ធ្វើនៅ	ंडो फिक्क हुंगा प्रतक्ति है। अस्तर हुंगा	3,00 र्षा क्षेत्र व्यव							

Maner Spin-42

Signal Si



ព្រះរាមារណាចត្រូកអង្គមា KINGDOM OF CAMBODIA មាតិ សាសខា ព្រះមហាក្សត្រ NATION RELIGION KING

की इस्मां सका

FAMILY RECORD BOOK

នាមគ្រះក្លាស្ត្ត SURNAME AND NAME 350. 5590 J

No 07655.11887

5. Agrasa. I.. 2012. 146

អាស័យដ្ឋាន

ADRESSE

ផ្ទះលេខ	្រុំមក្រុំ
CHEZ No.	GROUPE
វិថី	
RUE	
ภูษิ 🧲	30 BBB
VILLAGE	
ឃុំ_សង្កាត់	652678
COMMUNE-QUARTIE	R
ស្រុក_ខ័ណ្ឌ	652572
DISTRICT	
ខេត្ត_ក្រុង	<u> </u>
PROVINCE-VILLE	
	9,2 7 9 10 00
	ថ្ងៃទី <u>25</u> ខែ <u>10</u> ឆ្នាំ <u>199</u> 9
savenanesen har	tor the contract of the contra
ស្នងការនគរបាល់	red-lin
(COMMISSAIRE	DE LA ROLICE)
	THE STATE OF THE S
	វាសនីយ៍ទោ.អ៊ូ_ចាន់កុសល
	9

X	W	W	M		K		F		S	03	-	-	S	O			ល.រ	1		V
						1	SE SE		100	5/15	3	250	1000	35/16	100	31			100	
						/	13 2 1 CC	700	1635	8.435	2	to D	5=0	क्रिक्र	19 2	35	ซูโลโยบูเบ_ซูโลโล			
							5861	1000	1988	2861	8/	1861 60 H	1983	19.	10 10	2000		<u>ڪ</u> ڙ.		
						1	13/21	1	500	12100	1	The state of the s	id /	022	CZ,	5		9111	X	
						1	155		7	518		50	25	S. C. C.	1000		សេចិន្ត្រ	ED €	ទំនាក់ទំនង	
							Sensol Stage	28/18/1 N. 18/18/2	The Contract of the Contract o	3/12/2/2018	्रात्र क्षेत्र व्यक्त	1300 Sept 15 25 1	The said said	300	Selected Alexa	2/265	ស្រុក_ខ្ញុំឈ្នាំ ខេត្តក្នុក្កុង	ភូមិ. ឃុំ_សង្កាត់	ស្រុកកំណើត	Š
X							20	200	162	24	TO CO	5 627 5	~ O		ELL STATE OF THE PARTY OF THE P	20	1			چ
					ACS TO	4	2)/2	100	Dy 18	5/10	9 8	200	S C C C C C C C C C C C C C C C C C C C	网点多么	4	to f	កន្លែងធ្វើការ	នាដ	ınıch	ري و
												1833					3. 3. 3. 3. 3. 3. 3. 3. 3. 3. 3. 3. 3. 3	Wer one	211 GFU3	
							22 10 95	(10)	20 11 00	22 10 99	11 01 11	27 H GC	22 9116	22 10 95	12 01.17	20 10 00	เก็กเล้	200	3.5 20 30 30	
																	ធ្លាស់ទៅ_មក	តិវាទីកន្លែវា	ម្លៃ នូវ	
								2									Madan	Marina	000	

#